<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Creto | D2C Marketing Strategies</title>
    <description>The best marketing and growth strategies for D2C brands</description>
    <link>https://blog.creto.club//</link>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.creto.club//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 03:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 03:56:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.9.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Referral marketing for Indian brands: 5 ways to make your e-commerce referral program stand out</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you’re running a brand in India or are in the marketing team of one, you’ve definitely heard of referral marketing.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;With the sheer amount of digital noise and the number of brands that consumers are exposed to how do you make sure that your referral campaign works? &lt;em&gt;Today we’ll go over 5 very actionable tips crafted just for Indian brands. (P.S. number 4 is my favourite!)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Before we dive into the 5 points however, there is just one thing to keep in mind. Referral marketing is solely based on 1 underlying factor and 1 factor alone, and that is...</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 09:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://blog.creto.club//referral-marketing-for-indian-brands/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.creto.club//referral-marketing-for-indian-brands/</guid>
        
        <category>post purchase</category>
        
        <category>referral marketing</category>
        
        <category>blog</category>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to the Creto Blog!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Digital marketing is hard&lt;/strong&gt;. Social, search, paid, influencers, referrals and a ton of other stuff to stay upto date with constantly. What’s even harder is doing digital marketing well enough to build a successful brand.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;We’re building out this blog because there is a real lack of structured marketing content built specifically for consumer brands.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Marketing a brand is part art and part science. We’ll explain both.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;h2 id=&quot;about-me&quot;&gt;About Me&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;… dramatic music plays …&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I’m an engineer turned digital marketer for a sports brand in Mumbai. I have had the good fortune to be mentored directly by...</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 13:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://blog.creto.club//welcome-to-the-creto-blog/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.creto.club//welcome-to-the-creto-blog/</guid>
        
        <category>welcome</category>
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        <category>blog</category>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
